THAT
THAT I
THAT I MENTIONED
THAT I MENTIONED DEPEND
THAT I MENTIONED DEPEND ON
THAT I MENTIONED DEPEND ON YOU.
BUT
BUT YOU'RE
BUT YOU'RE JUST
BUT YOU'RE JUST ONE
BUT YOU'RE JUST ONE HUMAN
BUT YOU'RE JUST ONE HUMAN LIKE
WE
WE MENTIONED
WE MENTIONED MORTAL
WE MENTIONED MORTAL LIKE
WE MENTIONED MORTAL LIKE ALL
WE MENTIONED MORTAL LIKE ALL OF
US.
DO
DO YOU
DO YOU THINK
DO YOU THINK ABOUT
DO YOU THINK ABOUT YOUR
DO YOU THINK ABOUT YOUR MORTALITY?
ARE
ARE YOU
ARE YOU AFRAID
ARE YOU AFRAID OF
ARE YOU AFRAID OF DEATH?
>> I
>> I REALLY
>> I REALLY DON'T
>> I REALLY DON'T WANT
>> I REALLY DON'T WANT TO
>> I REALLY DON'T WANT TO DIE.
I
I HAVE
I HAVE A
I HAVE A GREAT
I HAVE A GREAT LIFE.
I
I HAVE
I HAVE A
I HAVE A GREAT
I HAVE A GREAT FAMILY.
I
I HAVE
I HAVE REALLY
I HAVE REALLY IMPORTANT
I HAVE REALLY IMPORTANT WORK.
THIS
THIS IS
THIS IS THIS
THIS IS THIS IS
THIS IS THIS IS NOT
THIS IS THIS IS NOT A
ONCE
ONCE IN
ONCE IN A
ONCE IN A ONCE
ONCE IN A ONCE IN
ONCE IN A ONCE IN A
LIFETIME
LIFETIME EXPERIENCE
LIFETIME EXPERIENCE SUGGESTS
LIFETIME EXPERIENCE SUGGESTS THAT
LIFETIME EXPERIENCE SUGGESTS THAT IT
LIFETIME EXPERIENCE SUGGESTS THAT IT HAS
BEEN
BEEN EXPERIENCED
BEEN EXPERIENCED BY
BEEN EXPERIENCED BY MANY
BEEN EXPERIENCED BY MANY PEOPLE
BEEN EXPERIENCED BY MANY PEOPLE JUST
NOT
NOT ONE
NOT ONE PERSON.
THIS
THIS IS
THIS IS A
THIS IS A ONCE
THIS IS A ONCE IN
THIS IS A ONCE IN A
HUMANITY
HUMANITY EXPERIENCE
HUMANITY EXPERIENCE WHAT
HUMANITY EXPERIENCE WHAT I'M
HUMANITY EXPERIENCE WHAT I'M GOING
HUMANITY EXPERIENCE WHAT I'M GOING THROUGH.
NVIDIA
NVIDIA IS
NVIDIA IS ONE
NVIDIA IS ONE OF
NVIDIA IS ONE OF THE
NVIDIA IS ONE OF THE MOST
CONSEQUENTIAL
CONSEQUENTIAL TECHNOLOGY